<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GlassRoom</title>
    <description>GlassRoom</description>
    <link>//</link>
    <atom:link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:35:19 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:35:19 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alice in Wonderland</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The rabbit-hole went straight on like a tunnel for some way, and then  dipped suddenly down, so suddenly that Alice had not a moment to think  about stopping herself before she found herself falling down a very deep  well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either the well was very deep, or she fell very slowly, for she had  plenty of time as she went down to look about her and to wonder what was  going to happen next. First, she tried to look down and make out what  she was coming to, but it was too dark to see anything; then she  looked at the sides of the well, and noticed that they were filled with  cupboards and book-shelves; here and there she saw maps and pictures  hung upon pegs. She took down a jar from one of the shelves as  she passed; it was labelled ‘ORANGE MARMALADE’, but to her great  disappointment it was empty: she did not like to drop the jar for fear  of killing somebody, so managed to put it into one of the cupboards as  she fell past it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Well!’ thought Alice to herself, ‘after such a fall as this, I shall  think nothing of tumbling down stairs! How brave they’ll all think me at  home! Why, I wouldn’t say anything about it, even if I fell off the top  of the house!’ (Which was very likely true.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down, down, down. Would the fall NEVER come to an end! ‘I wonder how  many miles I’ve fallen by this time?’ she said aloud. ‘I must be getting  somewhere near the centre of the earth. Let me see: that would be four  thousand miles down, I think—’ (for, you see, Alice had learnt several  things of this sort in her lessons in the schoolroom, and though this  was not a VERY good opportunity for showing off her knowledge, as there  was no one to listen to her, still it was good practice to say it over)  ‘—yes, that’s about the right distance—but then I wonder what Latitude  or Longitude I’ve got to?’ (Alice had no idea what Latitude was, or  Longitude either, but thought they were nice grand words to say.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presently she began again. ‘I wonder if I shall fall right THROUGH the  earth! How funny it’ll seem to come out among the people that walk with  their heads downward! The Antipathies, I think—’ (she was rather glad  there WAS no one listening, this time, as it didn’t sound at all the  right word) ‘—but I shall have to ask them what the name of the country  is, you know. Please, Ma’am, is this New Zealand or Australia?’ (and  she tried to curtsey as she spoke—fancy CURTSEYING as you’re falling  through the air! Do you think you could manage it?) ‘And what an  ignorant little girl she’ll think me for asking! No, it’ll never do to  ask: perhaps I shall see it written up somewhere.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down, down, down. There was nothing else to do, so Alice soon began  talking again. ‘Dinah’ll miss me very much to-night, I should think!’  (Dinah was the cat.) ‘I hope they’ll remember her saucer of milk at  tea-time. Dinah my dear! I wish you were down here with me! There are no  mice in the air, I’m afraid, but you might catch a bat, and that’s very  like a mouse, you know. But do cats eat bats, I wonder?’ And here Alice  began to get rather sleepy, and went on saying to herself, in a dreamy  sort of way, ‘Do cats eat bats? Do cats eat bats?’ and sometimes, ‘Do  bats eat cats?’ for, you see, as she couldn’t answer either question,  it didn’t much matter which way she put it. She felt that she was dozing  off, and had just begun to dream that she was walking hand in hand with  Dinah, and saying to her very earnestly, ‘Now, Dinah, tell me the truth:  did you ever eat a bat?’ when suddenly, thump! thump! down she came upon  a heap of sticks and dry leaves, and the fall was over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alice was not a bit hurt, and she jumped up on to her feet in a moment:  she looked up, but it was all dark overhead; before her was another  long passage, and the White Rabbit was still in sight, hurrying down it.  There was not a moment to be lost: away went Alice like the wind, and  was just in time to hear it say, as it turned a corner, 'Oh my ears  and whiskers, how late it's getting!' She was close behind it when she  turned the corner, but the Rabbit was no longer to be seen: she found  herself in a long, low hall, which was lit up by a row of lamps hanging  from the roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were doors all round the hall, but they were all locked; and when  Alice had been all the way down one side and up the other, trying every  door, she walked sadly down the middle, wondering how she was ever to  get out again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/Alice-in-Wonderland/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/Alice-in-Wonderland/</guid>
        
        <category>tag01</category>
        
        <category>tag02</category>
        
        
        <category>cat01</category>
        
        <category>cat02</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Scarlet Plague</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The boys laughed and lay down again in the sand, while Granser sighed  ponderously. He had eaten too much, and, with hands clasped on his  paunch, the fingers interlaced, he resumed his maunderings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;'The fleeting systems lapse like foam,'&quot; he mumbled what was evidently  a quotation. &quot;That's it&amp;mdash;foam, and fleeting. All man's toil upon the  planet was just so much foam. He domesticated the serviceable animals,  destroyed the hostile ones, and cleared the land of its wild vegetation.  And then he passed, and the flood of primordial life rolled back again,  sweeping his handiwork away&amp;mdash;the weeds and the forest inundated his  fields, the beasts of prey swept over his flocks, and now there are  wolves on the Cliff House beach.&quot; He was appalled by the thought. &quot;Where  four million people disported themselves, the wild wolves roam to-day,  and the savage progeny of our loins, with prehistoric weapons, defend  themselves against the fanged despoilers. Think of it! And all because  of the Scarlet Death&amp;mdash;&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The adjective had caught Hare-Lip's ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;He's always saying that,&quot; he said to Edwin. &quot;What is scarlet?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;'The scarlet of the maples can shake me like the cry of bugles going  by,'&quot; the old man quoted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;It's red,&quot; Edwin answered the question. &quot;And you don't know it because  you come from the Chauffeur Tribe. They never did know nothing, none of  them. Scarlet is red&amp;mdash;I know that.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Red is red, ain't it?&quot; Hare-Lip grumbled. &quot;Then what's the good of  gettin' cocky and calling it scarlet?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Granser, what for do you always say so much what nobody knows?&quot; he  asked. &quot;Scarlet ain't anything, but red is red. Why don't you say red,  then?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Red is not the right word,&quot; was the reply. &quot;The plague was scarlet.  The whole face and body turned scarlet in an hour's time. Don't I  know? Didn't I see enough of it? And I am telling you it was scarlet  because&amp;mdash;well, because it was scarlet. There is no other word for it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Red is good enough for me,&quot; Hare-Lip muttered obstinately. &quot;My dad  calls red red, and he ought to know. He says everybody died of the Red  Death.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/The-Scarlet-Plague/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/The-Scarlet-Plague/</guid>
        
        <category>tag03</category>
        
        <category>tag04</category>
        
        
        <category>cat03</category>
        
        <category>cat04</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Wizard of Oz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Now this same morning the Wicked Witch came to the door of her castle and looked out with her one eye that could see far off.  She saw all her wolves lying dead, and the strangers still traveling through her country.  This made her angrier than before, and she blew her silver whistle twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Straightway a great flock of wild crows came flying toward her, enough to darken the sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the Wicked Witch said to the King Crow, &quot;Fly at once to the strangers; peck out their eyes and tear them to pieces.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wild crows flew in one great flock toward Dorothy and her companions.  When the little girl saw them coming she was afraid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the Scarecrow said, &quot;This is my battle, so lie down beside me and you will not be harmed.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So they all lay upon the ground except the Scarecrow, and he stood up and stretched out his arms.  And when the crows saw him they were frightened, as these birds always are by scarecrows, and did not dare to come any nearer.  But the King Crow said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;It is only a stuffed man.  I will peck his eyes out.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The King Crow flew at the Scarecrow, who caught it by the head and twisted its neck until it died.  And then another crow flew at him, and the Scarecrow twisted its neck also.  There were forty crows, and forty times the Scarecrow twisted a neck, until at last all were lying dead beside him.  Then he called to his companions to rise, and again they went upon their journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the Wicked Witch looked out again and saw all her crows lying in a heap, she got into a terrible rage, and blew three times upon her silver whistle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forthwith there was heard a great buzzing in the air, and a swarm of black bees came flying toward her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/The-Wizard-of-Oz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/The-Wizard-of-Oz/</guid>
        
        <category>tag03</category>
        
        <category>tag04</category>
        
        
        <category>cat03</category>
        
        <category>cat04</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>At the Earth's Core</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Formerly he may have been as good to look upon as the others of his handsome race, and it may be that the terrible result of this encounter had tended to sour an already strong and brutal character.  However this may be it is quite certain that he was not a pretty sight, and now that his features, or what remained of them, were distorted in rage at the sight of Dian with another male, he was indeed most terrible to see&amp;mdash;and much more terrible to meet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had broken into a run now, and as he advanced he raised his mighty spear, while I halted and fitting an arrow to my bow took as steady aim as I could.  I was somewhat longer than usual, for I must confess that the sight of this awful man had wrought upon my nerves to such an extent that my knees were anything but steady.  What chance had I against this mighty warrior for whom even the fiercest cave bear had no terrors!  Could I hope to best one who slaughtered the sadok and dyryth single-handed!  I shuddered; but, in fairness to myself, my fear was more for Dian than for my own fate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then the great brute launched his massive stone-tipped spear, and I raised my shield to break the force of its terrific velocity.  The impact hurled me to my knees, but the shield had deflected the missile and I was unscathed.  Jubal was rushing upon me now with the only remaining weapon that he carried&amp;mdash;a murderous-looking knife.  He was too close for a careful bowshot, but I let drive at him as he came, without taking aim.  My arrow pierced the fleshy part of his thigh, inflicting a painful but not disabling wound.  And then he was upon me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My agility saved me for the instant.  I ducked beneath his raised arm, and when he wheeled to come at me again he found a sword's point in his face.  And a moment later he felt an inch or two of it in the muscles of his knife arm, so that thereafter he went more warily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a duel of strategy now&amp;mdash;the great, hairy man maneuvering to get inside my guard where he could bring those giant thews to play, while my wits were directed to the task of keeping him at arm's length. Thrice he rushed me, and thrice I caught his knife blow upon my shield. Each time my sword found his body&amp;mdash;once penetrating to his lung.  He was covered with blood by this time, and the internal hemorrhage induced paroxysms of coughing that brought the red stream through the hideous mouth and nose, covering his face and breast with bloody froth. He was a most unlovely spectacle, but he was far from dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the duel continued I began to gain confidence, for, to be perfectly candid, I had not expected to survive the first rush of that monstrous engine of ungoverned rage and hatred.  And I think that Jubal, from utter contempt of me, began to change to a feeling of respect, and then in his primitive mind there evidently loomed the thought that perhaps at last he had met his master, and was facing his end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At any rate it is only upon this hypothesis that I can account for his next act, which was in the nature of a last resort&amp;mdash;a sort of forlorn hope, which could only have been born of the belief that if he did not kill me quickly I should kill him.  It happened on the occasion of his fourth charge, when, instead of striking at me with his knife, he dropped that weapon, and seizing my sword blade in both his hands wrenched the weapon from my grasp as easily as from a babe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flinging it far to one side he stood motionless for just an instant glaring into my face with such a horrid leer of malignant triumph as to almost unnerve me&amp;mdash;then he sprang for me with his bare hands.  But it was Jubal's day to learn new methods of warfare.  For the first time he had seen a bow and arrows, never before that duel had he beheld a sword, and now he learned what a man who knows may do with his bare fists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As he came for me, like a great bear, I ducked again beneath his outstretched arm, and as I came up planted as clean a blow upon his jaw as ever you have seen.  Down went that great mountain of flesh sprawling upon the ground.  He was so surprised and dazed that he lay there for several seconds before he made any attempt to rise, and I stood over him with another dose ready when he should gain his knees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/At-the-Earth's-Core/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/At-the-Earth's-Core/</guid>
        
        <category>tag01</category>
        
        
        <category>cat02</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moby Dick</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Nearly all joined in singing this hymn, which swelled high above the howling of the storm. A brief pause ensued; the preacher slowly turned over the leaves of the Bible, and at last, folding his hand down upon the proper page, said: &quot;Beloved shipmates, clinch the last verse of the first chapter of Jonah&amp;mdash;'And God had prepared a great fish to swallow up Jonah.'&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Shipmates, this book, containing only four chapters&amp;mdash;four yarns&amp;mdash;is one of the smallest strands in the mighty cable of the Scriptures. Yet what depths of the soul does Jonah's deep sealine sound! what a pregnant lesson to us is this prophet! What a noble thing is that canticle in the fish's belly! How billow-like and boisterously grand! We feel the floods surging over us; we sound with him to the kelpy bottom of the waters; sea-weed and all the slime of the sea is about us! But WHAT is this lesson that the book of Jonah teaches? Shipmates, it is a two-stranded lesson; a lesson to us all as sinful men, and a lesson to me as a pilot of the living God. As sinful men, it is a lesson to us all, because it is a story of the sin, hard-heartedness, suddenly awakened fears, the swift punishment, repentance, prayers, and finally the deliverance and joy of Jonah. As with all sinners among men, the sin of this son of Amittai was in his wilful disobedience of the command of God&amp;mdash;never mind now what that command was, or how conveyed&amp;mdash;which he found a hard command. But all the things that God would have us do are hard for us to do&amp;mdash;remember that&amp;mdash;and hence, he oftener commands us than endeavors to persuade. And if we obey God, we must disobey ourselves; and it is in this disobeying ourselves, wherein the hardness of obeying God consists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;With this sin of disobedience in him, Jonah still further flouts at God, by seeking to flee from Him. He thinks that a ship made by men will carry him into countries where God does not reign, but only the Captains of this earth. He skulks about the wharves of Joppa, and seeks a ship that's bound for Tarshish. There lurks, perhaps, a hitherto unheeded meaning here. By all accounts Tarshish could have been no other city than the modern Cadiz. That's the opinion of learned men. And where is Cadiz, shipmates? Cadiz is in Spain; as far by water, from Joppa, as Jonah could possibly have sailed in those ancient days, when the Atlantic was an almost unknown sea. Because Joppa, the modern Jaffa, shipmates, is on the most easterly coast of the Mediterranean, the Syrian; and Tarshish or Cadiz more than two thousand miles to the westward from that, just outside the Straits of Gibraltar. See ye not then, shipmates, that Jonah sought to flee world-wide from God? Miserable man! Oh! most contemptible and worthy of all scorn; with slouched hat and guilty eye, skulking from his God; prowling among the shipping like a vile burglar hastening to cross the seas. So disordered, self-condemning is his look, that had there been policemen in those days, Jonah, on the mere suspicion of something wrong, had been arrested ere he touched a deck. How plainly he's a fugitive! no baggage, not a hat-box, valise, or carpet-bag,&amp;mdash;no friends accompany him to the wharf with their adieux. At last, after much dodging search, he finds the Tarshish ship receiving the last items of her cargo; and as he steps on board to see its Captain in the cabin, all the sailors for the moment desist from hoisting in the goods, to mark the stranger's evil eye. Jonah sees this; but in vain he tries to look all ease and confidence; in vain essays his wretched smile. Strong intuitions of the man assure the mariners he can be no innocent. In their gamesome but still serious way, one whispers to the other&amp;mdash;&quot;Jack, he's robbed a widow;&quot; or, &quot;Joe, do you mark him; he's a bigamist;&quot; or, &quot;Harry lad, I guess he's the adulterer that broke jail in old Gomorrah, or belike, one of the missing murderers from Sodom.&quot; Another runs to read the bill that's stuck against the spile upon the wharf to which the ship is moored, offering five hundred gold coins for the apprehension of a parricide, and containing a description of his person. He reads, and looks from Jonah to the bill; while all his sympathetic shipmates now crowd round Jonah, prepared to lay their hands upon him. Frighted Jonah trembles, and summoning all his boldness to his face, only looks so much the more a coward. He will not confess himself suspected; but that itself is strong suspicion. So he makes the best of it; and when the sailors find him not to be the man that is advertised, they let him pass, and he descends into the cabin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/Moby-Dick/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/Moby-Dick/</guid>
        
        <category>tag02</category>
        
        
        <category>cat03</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Around the World in 80 Days</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&quot;You're a sly dog!&quot; said Passepartout, winking at him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expression rather disturbed Fix, without his knowing why.  Had the Frenchman guessed his real purpose?  He knew not what to think.  But how could Passepartout have discovered that he was a detective?  Yet, in speaking as he did, the man evidently meant more than he expressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Passepartout went still further the next day; he could not hold his tongue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Mr. Fix,&quot; said he, in a bantering tone, &quot;shall we be so unfortunate as to lose you when we get to Hong Kong?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Why,&quot; responded Fix, a little embarrassed, &quot;I don't know; perhaps&amp;mdash;&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Ah, if you would only go on with us!  An agent of the Peninsular Company, you know, can't stop on the way!  You were only going to Bombay, and here you are in China.  America is not far off, and from America to Europe is only a step.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fix looked intently at his companion, whose countenance was as serene as possible, and laughed with him.  But Passepartout persisted in chaffing him by asking him if he made much by his present occupation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Yes, and no,&quot; returned Fix; &quot;there is good and bad luck in such things.  But you must understand that I don't travel at my own expense.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Oh, I am quite sure of that!&quot; cried Passepartout, laughing heartily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fix, fairly puzzled, descended to his cabin and gave himself up to his reflections.  He was evidently suspected; somehow or other the Frenchman had found out that he was a detective.  But had he told his master?  What part was he playing in all this: was he an accomplice or not?  Was the game, then, up?  Fix spent several hours turning these things over in his mind, sometimes thinking that all was lost, then persuading himself that Fogg was ignorant of his presence, and then undecided what course it was best to take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Placeholder text by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fillerati.com/&quot;&gt;Fillerati&lt;/a&gt;. Photography by &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/Around-the-World-in-80-Days/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/Around-the-World-in-80-Days/</guid>
        
        <category>tag03</category>
        
        
        <category>cat04</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BLOG IMAGE PERFORMANCE IS NECESSARY</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank &lt;a href=&quot;http://designyourownblog.com/about-dyob/&quot;&gt;Marianne&lt;/a&gt;, owner of &lt;a href=&quot;http://designyourownblog.com/&quot;&gt;DESIGN YOUR OWN BLOG&lt;/a&gt; who gave me permission to link to her post where she is talking about blog image performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Is blog image performance necessary?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Consider this:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Your users don’t want to wait more than 3 seconds for your page to load.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Google pays attention to your website speed and ranks it accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;So I’d say yes, it’s very necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Marianne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you care about your readers &lt;a href=&quot;http://designyourownblog.com/blog-image-performance/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; post is a &lt;b&gt;MUST READ&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There are 3 steps (4 for JPEGs) we should take to optimize our images:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Always resize the image to the largest size it will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Further reduce JPEG file size with these tricks.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Reduce quality on save.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Run it through a lossless image compression tool.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Marianne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Jekyll template was crafted in order to be used by photobloggers. If the photos you upload are not optimized, the page loading time will increase significantly! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;DO NOT upload an image at its full size, such as 2500 x 3500, and then resize it in the settings after you’ve uploaded it to your blog!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;– Marianne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt; So, dig in her informative post and learn how you can have a fast loading photography website!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://designyourownblog.com/blog-image-performance/&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;“THE BIGGEST MISTAKE YOU’RE PROBABLY MAKING WITH YOUR BLOG IMAGES + CHEAT SHEET”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you Marianne! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://designyourownblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/biggest-blog-mistake-image-performance-2.jpg&quot;&gt;Featured Image Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/images-size-for-better-performance/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/images-size-for-better-performance/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Multiple Galleries</title>
        <description>&lt;html class=&quot;no-js&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
	&lt;meta content=&quot;charset=utf-8&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;

    &lt;body&gt;

&lt;section id=&quot;content&quot; role=&quot;main&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;wrapper&quot;&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
			&lt;h2&gt;Multiple Galleries&lt;/h2&gt;




&lt;p&gt; Content of your post HERE &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Add as many paragraphs amongst your galleries as you want. &lt;/p&gt;


           &lt;!-- Gallery __--&gt;
			


&lt;div class=&quot;gallery masonry-gallery&quot;&gt;
  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g01/bg3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;!-- end of GALLERY __ --&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Add as many galleries as you want, including as many photos as you want. Simply edit the &lt;b&gt;FRONT MATTER&lt;/b&gt; of the post, adding the corresponding &lt;b&gt;path&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;caption&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;copyright&lt;/b&gt; info for each one of your photos. &lt;/p&gt;

           &lt;!-- Gallery __--&gt;
			


&lt;div class=&quot;gallery masonry-gallery&quot;&gt;
  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  

  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt;

	&lt;header class=&quot;gallery-icon&quot;&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;popup&quot; title=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot; data-caption=&quot;© photorama&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;//img/galleries/g02/bg3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
						
	&lt;/header&gt;	
		
   &lt;figcaption class=&quot;gallery-caption&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;entry-summary&quot; id=&quot;IMAGE TITLE&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;IMAGE TITLE&lt;/h3&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;© photorama&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/figcaption&gt;
				&lt;/figure&gt;

  
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;!-- end of GALLERY __ --&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- end of WRAPPER __ --&gt;
	&lt;/section&gt;


Photography by: &lt;a href=&quot;https://unsplash.com/photos/j0g8taxHZa0&quot;&gt;UNSPLASH&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>//journal/multiple-galleries/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//journal/multiple-galleries/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
